Christian Fowler

(470) 661-4923 | fowlerxchristian@gmail.com | Atlanta, Georgia linkedin.com/in/fowlerchristian/ | github.com/CFowlerx26

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detail-oriented problem solver with 350+ training hours and experience in Web development. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel as a web developer as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools JavaScript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 07/2023)

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS

- Bootstrap
- Unit Testing with Mocha
- Gi

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Web Developer Program | February 2023 - July 2023

Training Participant (in progress)

- Participating in a 22-week, 350+ hour Junior Web Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning fundamentals of JavaScript, programming fundamentals, developer tools, git and problem-solving

PerScholas Software Engineering Program | April 2022 - July 2022

Training Participant

- Actively participated in a 15-week, 350+ hour Software Engineering program
- Acquired skills in JavaScript, computer science concepts, frontend and backend frameworks, data structures, and algorithms.

Bank of America | Kennesaw, Georgia | November 2017 - February 2023

Credit Assistance Specialist

- Responsible for collections, customer service, submitting extension requests, other loss mitigation, and recovery activities on 80 plus incoming/outbound inquiries daily.
- Secure payments and determine reasons for delinquency on active or inactive loans, deposits, and/or credit card accounts.
- Navigate a computerized data entry system and other relevant applications while staying within regulatory and compliance guidelines within collections.

Home Depot | Marietta, Georgia | August 2015 - October 2017

Product Support Technician

- Help troubleshoot 50 plus online and store orders by remoting into PCs, running scripts, etc.
- Actively listen to and enable end-users with solutions to common problems.
- Participates in formal and informal training sessions to gain new skills and knowledge.

EDUCATION

Eastern Gateway Community College | Steubenville, Ohio | January 2022 - November 2024

• Internet/Digit Media Design | Dean's list May 2022 | Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society |